gats.io 2019-05-15

# Stats | gats.io - Player Stats | Customize - Upgrade - Compete

## Privacy Policy

This following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the website, gats.io.

Gats.io is committed to providing you with the best possible user experience. Gats.io is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), which sets out a number of principles concerning the privacy of individuals.

**Third-Party Advertising**

Some of the services and advertisements included on gats.io are delivered or served by third-party companies, which may collect information about your use of gats.io.

These companies place or recognize cookies, pixel tags, web beacons or other technology to track certain information about gats.io users. For example, in the course of serving certain advertisements, an advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of gats.io. For another example, an advertiser or ad server may also be able to collect your device’s unique identifier in the course of serving an ad. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads on other websites based on your interests.

We do not have access to, or control these third parties' use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used.

For example, we use Google to serve advertisements on gats.io, which use the Google Ad Manager/Google DoubleClick cookie, and in some cases, a unique device identifier, to show you ads based on your visit to gats.io, and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the Google Ad Manager/Google DoubleClick cookie by visiting [the Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://adssettings.google.com/). If you would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit <http://optout.aboutads.info/#/> and <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#>. You may download the AppChoices app at <http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices> to opt out in mobile apps.

Your access to gats.io should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.

**Collection of your personal information**

There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to future gats.io features you may be required to submit personally identifiable information. This may include but not limited to a unique username and password, or provide sensitive information in the recovery of your lost password.

**Sharing of your personal information**

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or database maintenance. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. Gats.io takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

**Use of your personal information**

For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this site.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only, data collected from the time of the policy change forward will adhere to our updated practices.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Gats.io reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy at any time. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.

**Accessing Your Personal Information**

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons. Gats.io reserves the right to charge a fee for searching for, and providing access to, your information on a per request basis.

**Contacting us**

Gats.io welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us at [contact@gats.io](mailto:contact@gats.io?Subject=Privacy)

**About us**

You can read more about gats.io here.
